Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.asia [Admin.@YNG]
=Lust and Lies=
=الشهوة والكذب=
The Lion Seal is lost.
لقد ضاع أسد البحر.
Huo Xiu has run away.
لقد هرب Huo Xiu.
If so,
إذا كان الأمر كذلك،
I'll look into it on your behalf.
سأنظر في الأمر نيابة عنك.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
This was found in the account at Henglong Bank.
تم العثور على هذا في الحساب في بنك هينجلونج.
Did you expect to see
هل كنت تتوقع أن ترى
some immeasurable wealth in this account as well?
بعض الثروة التي لا يمكن قياسها في هذا الحساب أيضًا؟
What's inside this briefcase
ماذا يوجد داخل هذه الحقيبة
is the most important wealth to us.
هي الثروة الأهم بالنسبة لنا.
My mother
والدتي
never stopped trying to clean my father's name
لم أتوقف أبدًا عن محاولة تنظيف اسم والدي
and exposing Huo Beishan.
وفضح هوو بيشان.
She hid all evidence
لقد أخفت كل الأدلة
in this briefcase.
في هذه الحقيبة.
That means
وهذا يعني
the rumor about the Lion Seal is fake.
الشائعة حول أسد البحر كاذبة.
Changqing.
تشانغتشينغ.
I've spread the word about the Lion Seal.
لقد نشرت الكلمة عن أسد البحر.
The human heart is greedy.
القلب البشري جشع.
Everyone will be greedy enough to fight over the Lion Seal.
سيكون الجميع جشعين بما يكفي للقتال على ختم الأسد.
When the fortune is found,
عندما يتم العثور على الثروة،
that will be the day
هذا سيكون اليوم
the Huo family meets their demise.
عائلة هوو تلتقي بحتميتها.
Mother.
الأم.
Are you alright?
هل انت بخير؟
Xiu.
شيو.
Listen up.
استمع جيدا.
If I die,
إذا مت
you must keep searching for evidence.
يجب عليك الاستمرار في البحث عن الأدلة.
You must watch the Huo family
يجب عليك مشاهدة عائلة هوو
fall into disgrace.
الوقوع في العار.
What a brilliant plot, you've managed to keep your hands clean.
يا لها من خطة رائعة، لقد تمكنت من الحفاظ على نظافة يديك.
You've actually been doing this for so many years.
لقد كنت تفعل هذا بالفعل لسنوات عديدة.
You've put up with all in the Huo Residence for so long
لقد تحملت كل شيء في Huo Residence لفترة طويلة
to search for evidence?
للبحث عن الأدلة؟
Boss Ruan
الرئيس روان
never told you what happened back then?
لم أخبرك بما حدث حينها؟
Father only said that Huo Beishan wanted to silence witnesses,
قال الأب فقط أن هوو بيشان أراد إسكات الشهود،
so he set our house on fire.
فأشعل النار في منزلنا.
As for the reason,
أما السبب،
he never once mentioned it.
ولم يذكر ذلك مطلقا.
It's fortunate you're not Huo Qingwan.
من حسن الحظ أنك لست هوو تشينغوان.
And luckily, you don't bear the Huo name.
ولحسن الحظ أنك لا تحمل اسم هوو.
=Episode 20=
=الحلقة 20=
Mr. Sheng.
السيد شنغ.
You know you adore Miss Qingwan.
أنت تعلم أنك تعشق الآنسة تشينغوان.
Only you can save her now.
أنت وحدك من يستطيع إنقاذها الآن.
Why did you say so?
لماذا قلت ذلك؟
Governor has dispatched the hitmen.
أرسل المحافظ القتلة المأجورين.
The Huo Army is also on its way there.
جيش هوو في طريقه إلى هناك أيضًا.
You want me
انت تريدني
to save Huo Xiu together?
لإنقاذ هوو شيو معًا؟
Fine.
بخير.
I'll go save him.
سأذهب لإنقاذه.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
You actually believed what I said.
لقد صدقت فعلا بما قلته.
With idiots like you around him,
مع وجود أغبياء مثلك حوله،
no wonder Huo Xiu is all useless.
لا عجب أن هوو شيو عديم الفائدة على الإطلاق.
Don't you know
ألا تعلم؟
the one I hate most is Huo Xiu?
الذي أكرهه أكثر هو هوو شيو؟
You heard it all on that day, no?
لقد سمعت كل ذلك في ذلك اليوم، أليس كذلك؟
The conversation between me and Governor.
الحوار بيني وبين المحافظ.
You're going to silence me?
هل تريد إسكاتي؟
Young Marshal, you're truly a skilled shooter.
أيها المارشال الشاب، أنت مطلق نار ماهر حقًا.
Put the gun down slowly.
ضع البندقية إلى الأسفل ببطء.
Hurry up!
عجلوا!
That's it.
هذا كل شيء.
Slowly.
ببطء.
That's the way it is.
هكذا هو الأمر.
Goodbye!
مع السلامة!
Feifei!
فيفي!
♪It's you in the blur of light and shadow♪
♪أنت في ضباب الضوء والظل♪
♪Our first encounter left me in awe for a lifetime♪
♪لقد تركني لقاءنا الأول في حالة من الرهبة مدى الحياة♪
♪Feelings I can't shake off♪
♪مشاعر لا أستطيع التخلص منها♪
♪Quietly emerge♪
♪الظهور بهدوء♪
♪It was just a single glance♪
♪كانت مجرد نظرة واحدة♪
♪A moment apart feels like endless years♪
♪لحظة فراق تبدو وكأنها سنوات لا نهاية لها♪
♪Amidst the light and shadow♪
♪وسط الضوء والظل♪
♪Love and hate blur together♪
♪الحب والكراهية يختلطان معًا♪
♪Why let ourselves fall deeper than we already are?♪
♪لماذا نسمح لأنفسنا بالسقوط بشكل أعمق مما نحن عليه بالفعل؟♪
You're finally awake.
لقد استيقظت أخيرا.
I thought
اعتقدت
- I'd lose you.
- سأخسرك.
♪You remain the same♪
♪أنت تبقى كما أنت♪
♪A longing I can never get over, like mist, like dreams♪
♪شوق لا يمكنني التغلب عليه أبدًا، مثل الضباب، مثل الأحلام♪
I won't let you die on me.
لن أدعك تموت علي.
What's the matter?
ماذا جرى؟
Cheng is missing.
تشنغ مفقود.
He's the only one I can trust in the residence.
إنه الشخص الوحيد الذي أستطيع أن أثق به في الإقامة.
He's my closest brother.
إنه أخي الأقرب.
I understand.
أفهم.
Just like Zhao Xun.
تماما مثل تشاو شون.
He was the kindest to me
لقد كان لطيفًا معي
in the Huofeng Gang.
في عصابة هووفنغ.
Huo Beishan.
هوو بيشان.
He must pay for what he did to them.
يجب أن يدفع ثمن ما فعله بهم.
These are the arms you moved
هذه هي الأذرع التي حركتها
during the festival to welcome the deity?
خلال المهرجان للترحيب بالإله؟
Yes.
نعم.
Who would have thought
من كان يظن
they'd end up in your hands?
هل سينتهي بهم الأمر بين يديك؟
Take your time to recuperate.
خذ وقتك للتعافي.
I will avenge the Ruan family for you.
سأنتقم لعائلة روان من أجلك.
Spare the First Madam.
انقذوا السيدة الأولى.
I think
أظن
they've waited long
لقد انتظروا طويلا
for this day to come, no?
لهذا اليوم قادم، أليس كذلك؟
The night is cold and damp.
الليل بارد ورطب.
Relight the lantern.
أعد إشعال الفانوس.
Newspaper for sale!
جريدة للبيع!
Clearing the Gu family's name.
تبرئة اسم عائلة جو.
The Huo family are in fact traitors.
عائلة هوو هم في الحقيقة خونة.
Newspaper for sale!
جريدة للبيع!
Father.
أب.
Sucheng has descended into chaos.
لقد انحدر سوتشنغ إلى الفوضى.
We should leave together.
ينبغي علينا أن نغادر معًا.
Here comes the best opportunity,
وهنا تأتي أفضل فرصة،
so I can't leave.
لذلك لا أستطيع المغادرة.
If so, we'll put it in the papers soon
إذا كان الأمر كذلك، فسوف نضعه في الصحف قريبًا
and annul the engagement with the Huo family.
وإلغاء الخطوبة مع عائلة هوو.
We shall sever our ties.
سوف نقطع علاقاتنا.
No.
لا.
Let's
دعونا
see how it goes and carry on with the marriage alliance.
انظر كيف تسير الأمور واستمر في تحالف الزواج.
That's a risky move.
هذه خطوة محفوفة بالمخاطر.
If we take a wrong step,
إذا اتخذنا خطوة خاطئة،
we will lose everything.
سوف نخسر كل شيء.
I intend to risk it all.
أنا أنوي المخاطرة بكل شيء.
Beishan.
بيشان.
This time, is our family
هذه المرة هي عائلتنا
truly done for?
هل تم الانتهاء منه حقا؟
It's done for?
هل انتهى الأمر؟
Despite all those rumors
على الرغم من كل تلك الشائعات
and them calling me a traitor,
وهم ينادونني بالخائن،
my family has numerous troops.
عائلتي لديها قوات عديدة.
Who dares oppose me?
من يجرؤ على معارضتي؟
Guards,
حراس،
order all of the Huo Army
أمر كل جيش هوو
to return to Sucheng!
للعودة إلى سوتشنغ!
♪Listen, the bell rings from afar♪
♪استمع، الجرس يرن من بعيد♪
♪The fog lifts, your image still hazy♪
♪يرتفع الضباب، وصورتك لا تزال ضبابية♪
♪Do you remember the sound of the flute in the wind?♪
♪هل تتذكر صوت الناي في الريح؟♪
♪It whispers of the flame we shared♪
♪همس من اللهب الذي شاركناه♪
♪Having seen those prophecies left behind♪
♪بعد أن رأيت تلك النبوءات التي تركوها وراءهم♪
♪A sudden will to survive arises♪
♪تنشأ فجأة رغبة في البقاء♪
♪The ruan resounds with grandeur♪
♪الروان يتردد صداه بالعظمة♪
♪Under the pelting plum rain♪
♪تحت المطر الغزير من البرقوق♪
♪Everyone sings the final act♪
♪الجميع يغني الفصل الأخير♪
♪All fading away♪
♪كل شيء يتلاشى♪
♪The curtain falls♪
♪الستار يسقط♪